Guide to the Paul Venable Turner Papers SC0948
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2018-073
  - The Ruth Lucie Stern Research Building of the Stanford Medical School
    - The buildings of Birge Clark and David Clark. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Birge and David Clark, miscellaneous information. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Turner's meetings and correspondence with Birge Clark's sons. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Research Material for Selected Articles
    - Research material for, and offprint of: "Frank Lloyd Wright's Other Larkin Building," in Journal of the Society of Architectural Historians, vol. XXXIX, no. 4, December 1980, pp 304-06. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Research material for, and offprints of: "Claude-Nicolas Ledoux and the Hypnerotomachia Polifili," in Word Image, vol 14, no. 1/2, January-June 1998, pp 203-14. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Research material for, and photocopy of: "The Campus as Palimpsest: Layers of History at Phillips Academy," in Academy Hill: The Andover Campus, 1778 to the Present (New York, Princeton Architectural Press, 2000), pp 1-30, 192-96. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - List of Paul V. Turner's Publications, and Offprints or Copies of Selected Items
    - "The Beginnings of Le Corbusier's Education, 1902-07," in The Art Bulletin, June 1971, pp 214-24. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Frank Lloyd Wright and the Young Le Corbusier," in Journal of the Society of Architectural Historians, December 1983, pp 350-59. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Architecture as Memorial: The Design of Stanford," in The Stanford Magazine, Spring/Summer 1975, pp 50-56. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "The Library That Never Was," in The Imprint of the Stanford Libraries Associates, April 1976, pp 4-13. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Joseph-Jacques Ramée's First Career," in The Art Bulletin, June 1985, pp 259-77. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "David Parish's Country House Reconstructed," in The Quarterly of the St. Lawrence County [NY] Historical Association, October 1986, pp 3-9. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Some Thoughts on History and Campus Planning," in Planning for Higher Education, vol. 16, no. 3, 1987-88, pp 1-28. "Searching for Ramée," in Union College Magazine, January 1997, pp 14-19. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright's Hanna House Restored [booklet], Stanford University [produced by the Development Office], 1999. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Quelques Réflexions sur l'histoire et l'aménagement des campus américains," in Histoire de l'Education, May 2004, pp 71-86. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Grand Design: Joseph Ramée's Drawings for the Union College Campus [exhibition catalogue], Union College, Schenectady, New York, 2013. (Box 2, Folder 30)